Mateo Dundek



mateo.dundek94@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/mateo-dundek-5bb39014b



+447885499412



https://mateodundek.github.io/MateoDundek_Eportfolio/

Summary

I'm a 29 year old from Croatia, living and working in the UK. Currently I have a full-time job in the security industry. Looking for a change in my career!

In my free time I'm learning and exploring new opportunities to become a Frontend Developer.

Given an opportunity to work as a Frontend Software Developer, I would do my best to catch up with company and team requirements and even take extra courses if needed.

Experience

Security Officer

G4S

Sep 2022 - Present (9 months) Security and customer service

Sous Chef

Oakman Inns & Restaurants Ltd

Aug 2021 - Jun 2022 (11 months)

Preparing and cooking food, got promoted to Sous chef in February 2022

Michaelle Chef

Mitchells & Butlers PLC Aug 2020 - Aug 2021 (1 year 1 month) Preparing and cooking food



Frankie & Benny's Jan 2019 - Jul 2020 (1 year 7 months) Counting stock, perparing and cooking food

Repairer

Plava Laguna Jul 2018 - Nov 2018 (5 months) Maintenance of pool techniques

Factory Worker

ESCO Pte. Ltd.

Oct 2017 - Mar 2018 (6 months)

Quality management and control

#POB Factory Worker

#POB

Mar 2016 - Oct 2017 (1 year 8 months) Worker on the welding line and machine maintenance

Electrician

ELEKTROMETAL

Sep 2015 - Dec 2015 (4 months) Company went bankrupt

Education



Technical School Bjelovar

Skills

css • html • microsoft office • microsoft windows • Software • Hardware • React.js • Customer Service • JavaScript